Aiyet
What?
What’s wrong with you again?
Aiyet
Come out here right now!
Hao Ruichi
You...
Your nosebleed... it's blue?
You're really an alien!
His crystal is still intact!
You’re definitely not from here.
If you still don’t believe it,
then there’s something seriously wrong with your IQ.
Oh my god!
You messing up my life all the time is one thing,
but don’t make it this bizarre!
Wait a second...
If...
you’re not from around here,
then why did you come to Earth?
You're not planning to experiment on me, right?
I...
am here to capture a fugitive.
Capture someone?
A highly dangerous fugitive from Lanke Star
escaped to Earth.
I followed him here.
Aiyet
Never would I have thought,
that I, Aiyet,
could draw the attention of a true Lanke Star Envoy to come after me.
You can't defeat me.
Come back with me quietly.
I know I can’t beat you.
But Lanke Star...
I don’t want to spend another second there.
Goodbye!
Your Excellency the Envoy,
Aiyet!
I order you to stop!
Goodbye, Hao Ruichi.
I’ll never go back again.
Preparing for teleportation...
Intergalactic jump to unknown coordinates...
Highly dangerous.
Please proceed with caution.
Teleportation.
That's so amazing!
A face is also made of flesh.
Then how are we any different?
Could it be...
That the body's structure is different?
Qi Miao,
don't test my limits.
Sorry!
I just got too excited for a moment.
Anyway,
until I capture the fugitive
and fully replenish my energy,
I'll have to stay here.
So,
I hope you adjust your attitude
and stop treating me
like some kind of pervert.
Living together all the time—
isn't that really dangerous?
Living with me is your good fortune.
Besides,
I need your help to replenish my crystal energy.
Replenish energy?
Exactly.
We Lankexing people, when on other planets,
rely on energy crystals
to release energy.
And you,
like me, are an Omega-type person.
So your magnetic field can help restore my energy.
Omega-type person?
Of course.
You Earthlings can't see your own magnetic fields—
that's completely normal.
But from what I've observed,
your magnetic fields are divided into hundreds of types.
And yours happens to be the same type as mine.
I'm just usually unlucky.
So, does that mean you're as unlucky as I am?
No.
What you call 'luck'
has nothing to do with the type of magnetic field.
The reason you're unlucky
is because of your mindset,
your actions,
which cause the gaps in your magnetic field to widen.
I can help you
fill in the magnetic field gaps.
The gap is widening.
I can't understand a thing!
Can I interpret it as
you can help me change my luck?
That's right.
As long as you follow my instructions obediently,
I can help you change your luck.
Change my luck?
And you're making me spend money?
I just spent half my monthly salary!
Shopping can change my luck?
No,
I simply need new clothes.
Wait,
didn't you promise to help me change my luck?
Yes.
Haven't you noticed?
Since this morning,
your luck has already shifted.
What do you mean?
At eight this morning, after breakfast,
you accidentally knocked over a vinegar bottle,
but it fell perfectly into a box and didn't break.
At nine,
when you took out the trash,
a slipper near the door propped it open,
so you didn't get locked outside.
At noon when you were about to do laundry,
you got a phone call,
which reminded you to take your phone out of the dirty laundry pocket.
Those are just coincidences.
Exactly.
But no one is naturally unlucky.
What we consider bad luck
is just a series of coincidental events stacking up.
You're just overly focused on these incidents.
This mental block changes your magnetic field
and attracts even more unfortunate events.
What are you saying?
This sounds like a self-help cliché!
Why do I feel like believing you
is less effective than going to a temple to pray?
It's because you can't see the changes in the magnetic field
that you start believing in these illusory things.
I can tell you very clearly,
judging by the changes in your energy field,
something joyful is about to happen to you.
Qi Xiaomiao,
you've won!
You've scored tickets to Allen's concert!
Really?
Wait a moment,
let me check.
What do you think?
Hao Ruichi,
you're amazing!
It's simple.
Am I dreaming?
For something like this to happen to you,
it sure feels unreal.
I can't believe that over such a small thing,
you're all this happy.
You Earthlings,
are indeed quite peculiar.
Earthlings?
Oh, and who is this handsome guy?
I am an envoy from the Blue Core Star.
He's just an old classmate of mine from the countryside.
Recently, he came to the city and didn’t have a place to stay,
so he's sharing a rental with me at my place.
We're roommates now.
I,
have a feeling there's more to your relationship.
More to it?
It's simpler than your name itself.
I see it’s getting late.
We should head home now.
See you at the concert!
Wait,
you hardly get new friends visiting,
so I’ve got to let you taste my newly invented dish!
Qi Miao, stop right there!
This time my dish is really delicious!
Next time, definitely next time!
Not a single customer during meal rush hour?
Am I really not cut out for cooking?
What's that?
Who’s there?
Who are you?